Guide to the Washington Metropolitan Area Transit Authority (WMATA) photographs, audiovisual, and publications, 1944-2014 MS2374
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Photographic material and paper records, Series 1
  - Color slides, Series 1 Subseries 4
    - Staff: Facilities Maintenance 3, April 1986 - September 1987; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 90, Folder 7)
    - Staff: Facilities Maintenance 4, December 1987 - September 1989; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 90, Folder 8)
    - Staff: Facilities Maintenance 5, June 1989 - October 1991; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 90, Folder 9)
    - Staff: Accounting, Admin, ADSV, December 1978 - September 2000; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 91, Folder 1)
    - Staff: Annual Awards, Arch, Audit, March 1981 - September 1998; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 91, Folder 2)
    - Staff: Budget, BUSV, March 1985 - September 1998; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 91, Folder 3)
    - Staff: BUSV Awards, April 1983 - June 1988; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 91, Folder 4)
    - Staff: Bus Depot Clerk, Quality Assurance, April 1985 - September 1998; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 91, Folder 5)
    - Staff: Bus Operators 1, April 1973 - April 1991; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 91, Folder 6)
    - Staff: Bus Operators 2, April 1991 - August 2002; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 91, Folder 7)
    - Special Events 2, October 1994 - December 2001; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 92, Folder 1)
    - Staff 1, January 1966 - August 1967; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 92, Folder 2)
    - Staff 2, February 1967 - June 1968; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 92, Folder 3)
    - Staff 3, June 1968 - December 1970; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 92, Folder 4)
    - Staff 4, December 1970 - December 1972; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 92, Folder 5)
    - Staff 5, January 1973 - May 1974; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 92, Folder 6)
    - Staff 6, May 1974 - September 1985; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 92, Folder 7)
    - Staff: ADA, October 1992 - November 2002; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 92, Folder 8)
    - Scenic: Crystal City, FDR Memorial, Holocaust Museum, October 1977 - August 1998; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 94, Folder 1)
    - Scenic: Jefferson and Lincoln Memorial, National Zoo, May 1978 - June 2002; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 94, Folder 2)
    - Scenic: Smithsonian 1, May 1978 - June 2002; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 94, Folder 3)
    - Scenic: Smithsonian 2, May 1978 - June 2002; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 94, Folder 4)
    - Scenic: War Memorials, White House, July 1984 - June 2004; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 94, Folder 5)
    - Signs 1, March 1963 - June 1982; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 94, Folder 6)
    - Signs 2: Snow, Special Events, December 1975 - September 2001; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 94, Folder 7)
    - Special Events 1, January 1984 - October 1994; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 94, Folder 8)
    - Scenic: Capitol and Washington Monuments, Chinatown, May 1967 - October 2003; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 95, Folder 1)
    - Scenic: Assorted, November 1968 - February 1989; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 95, Folder 2)
    - Scenic: Assorted 2, February 1989 - December 1995; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 95, Folder 3)
    - Scenic: Assorted 3, December 1995 - September 1998; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 95, Folder 4)
    - Scenic: Assorted 4, December 1998 - September 2003; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 95, Folder 5)
    - Scenic: Aerial 1, January 1977 - May 1987; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 95, Folder 6)
    - Scenic: Aerial 2, May 1987 - March 1988; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 95, Folder 7)
    - Safety, February 1975 - October 1989; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 95, Folder 8)
    - Repairs, Train Revenue Collection, Roads, May 1975 - March 1987; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 95, Folder 9)
    - Real Estate, Redskins, September 1970 - January 1992; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 95, Folder 10)
    - Rails, Rail Orientation, April 1963 - August 1983; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 96, Folder 1)
    - Promotion, August 1965 - June 1989; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 96, Folder 2)
    - Posters 1, April 1974 - October 1996; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 96, Folder 3)
    - Posters 2, May 1996 - May 2004; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 96, Folder 4)
    - Parking, Park 'N Ride, Pope, March 1963 - October 1979; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 96, Folder 5)
    - Opening Day: Trains, Yellow Line (Gallery-Nat'l), March 1976 - May 1983; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 96, Folder 6)
    - Opening Day: Waterfront Station, December 1991; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 96, Folder 7)
    - Opening Day: West Falls Church, Wheaton, White Flint, Woodley Park Zoo, December 1981 - September 1990; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 96, Folder 8)
    - Opening Day: Union Station, Van Ness-UDC, Vienna, Virginia Square, March 1976 - June 1991; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 96, Folder 9)
    - Opening Day: Shady Grove, Shaw-Howard U, Silver Spring, Twinbrook, U Street-Cardozo, February 1978 - May 1991; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 97, Folder 1)
    - Opening Day: Rockville, Rosslyn, July 1977 - December 1984; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 97, Folder 2)
    - Opening Day: Rhode Island Ave, March 1976; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 97, Folder 3)
    - Opening Day: King Street, L'Enfant Plaza, Metro Center, Mt. Vernon Square, March 1976 - May 1991; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 97, Folder 4)
    - Opening Day: Grosvenor Sta., Huntington, Judiciary Square, March 1976 - August 1984; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 97, Folder 5)
    - Opening Day: Green Line, Georgia Ave - Petworth, Glenmont, Greenbelt, May 1991 - September 1999; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 97, Folder 6)
    - Opening Day: Fort Totten, Friendship Heights, February 1978 - December 1993; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 97, Folder 7)
    - Opening Day: Eisenhower Ave. to Franconia-Springfield, March 1976 - June 1997; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 97, Folder 8)
    - March on Washington, August 1980 - August 1983; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 98, Folder 1)
    - Minorities, December 1970 - March 1972; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 98, Folder 2)
    - New Carrollton Shop, News 1, May 1967 - December 1981; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 98, Folder 3)
    - News 2, September 1977 - March 1991; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 98, Folder 4)
    - News Clips, OCCB, January 1962 - December 1991; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 98, Folder 5)
    - Opening Day: Anacostia, December 1991; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 98, Folder 6)
    - Opening Day: Ballston, Bethesda, Branch Ave, Braddock Rd, Brookland, February 1978 - January 2001; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 98, Folder 7)
    - Opening Day: Clarendon, Cleveland Park, Columbia Heights, Courthouse, Crystal City, July 1977 - January 2001; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 98, Folder 8)
    - Opening Day: Dunn Loring to East Falls Church, January 1977 - June 1986; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 98, Folder 9)
    - Independence Day 4, July 1987 - July 1994; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 99, Folder 1)
    - Kiosk, Kiss and Ride, Learning Lab, Leisure 1, May 1968 - December 1977; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 99, Folder 2)
    - Leisure 2, October 1968 - August 1969; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 99, Folder 3)
    - Leisure 3, August 1969 - July 1975; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 99, Folder 4)
    - Leisure 4, July 1975; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 99, Folder 5)
    - Logo, Maps 1, January 1962 - February 2001; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 99, Folder 6)
    - Maps 2, March 1969 - February 1983; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 99, Folder 7)
    - Maps 3, February 1983 - May 2001; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 99, Folder 8)
    - Groundbreaking: U-Street, Virginia, Van Dorn, West Hyattsville, June 1971 - May 1987; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 100, Folder 1)
    - Groundbreaking: Wheaton, November 1983; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 100, Folder 2)
    - Hearings, January 1974 - March 1979; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 100, Folder 3)
    - Humor, April 1962 - March 1987; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 100, Folder 4)
    - Inauguration, January 1977 - January 1997; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 100, Folder 5)
    - Independence Day 1, July 1978 - July 1983; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 100, Folder 6)
    - Independence Day 2, July 1983 - July 1984; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 100, Folder 7)
    - Independence Day 3, July 1986 - July 1987; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 100, Folder 8)
    - Equipment - Maintenance, Rail, Safety, Park, February 1985 - December 1998; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 101, Folder 1)
    - Equipment - Snow Removal, Track, March 1982 - December 1998; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 101, Folder 2)
    - Equipment - Trains, February 1969 - May 2002; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 101, Folder 3)
    - Equipment - Vehicles, Hazardous Waste Sites, October 1981 - June 1996; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 101, Folder 4)
    - Farecard, Filming, Fireworks, February 1970 - August 1999; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 101, Folder 5)
    - Exhibits, August 1968 - January 2002; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 101, Folder 6)
    - Graphics: Bus Posters, Metro Manual, Pylon, Train Destination, January 1968 - March 1990; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 101, Folder 7)
    - Groundbreaking: Anacostia, June 1976 - February 1994; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 101, Folder 8)
    - Groundbreaking: Huntington, Judiciary Square, January 1969 - June 1977; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 101, Folder 9)
    - Groundbreaking: Largo, Landover, PG County, Rosslyn, Silver Spring, June 1971 - May 2001; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 101, Folder 10)
    - Construction K-6, May 1972 - November 1984; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 102, Folder 1)
    - Construction K-7 Vienna, Construction K-8 West Falls Church, November 1979 - November 1984; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 102, Folder 2)
    - Construction L-1, September 1976 - November 1979; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 102, Folder 3)
    - Construction L-2a, L-2b, August 1974 - August 1976; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 102, Folder 4)
    - Elderly and Disabled, August 1975 - May 1986; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 102, Folder 5)
    - Engineering 1, April 1962 - April 1970; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 102, Folder 6)
    - Engineering 2, February 1971 - May 1988; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 102, Folder 7)
    - Construction G-1, G-2, G-3, May 1978 - August 1980; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 103, Folder 1)
    - Construction: Largo Extension Prep, September 2001 - November 2001; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 103, Folder 2)
    - Construction: G4a Garrett Morgan, April 2002 - May 2003; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 103, Folder 3)
    - Construction: G4a Largo Town Center, December 2001 - May 2003; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 103, Folder 4)
    - Construction: G4al Largo Alignment, April 2002 - October 2002; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 103, Folder 5)
    - Construction: G4al Largo Extension (Central Ave), March 2002 - December 2002; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 103, Folder 6)
    - Construction: G4b Largo Extension (Tunnels), July 2002 - October 2002; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 103, Folder 7)
    - Construction: G4al Largo (Beltway Bridge), December 2001 - May 2003; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 103, Folder 8)
    - Construction: N.Y. Ave. (In-Line), October 2001 - July 2002; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 103, Folder 9)
    - Construction: H-1 1 Franconia-Springfield, March 1993 - October 1993; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 103, Folder 10)
    - Construction: H-1 2 Franconia-Springfield, October 1993 - April 1996; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 103, Folder 11)
    - Construction: H-1 3 Franconia-Springfield, April 1996 - March 1997; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 103, Folder 12)
    - Construction: J-1, J-2, July 1987 - April 1995; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 103, Folder 13)
    - Construction: K-1, August 1974 - April 1979; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 103, Folder 14)
    - Construction: K-2, K-3, May 1974 - April 1979; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 103, Folder 15)
    - Construction: K-4 Ballston, May 1974 - April 1979; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 103, Folder 16)
    - Construction: E-5, March 1989 - April 1993; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 104, Folder 1)
    - Construction: E-6, March 1987 - November 1990; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 104, Folder 2)
    - Construction: E-7, May 1988 - September 1991; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 104, Folder 3)
    - Construction: E-9, December 1989 - October 1991; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 104, Folder 4)
    - Construction: E-10, December 1985 - October 1991; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 104, Folder 5)
    - Construction: E-11 Greenbelt Yard, October 1991; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 104, Folder 6)
    - Construction: F Route Aerials & Ground, May 1982; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 104, Folder 7)
    - Construction: F-1a, March 1974 - November 1982; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 104, Folder 8)
    - Construction: F-1b, July 1973 - November 1982; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 104, Folder 9)
    - Construction: F-2, July 1975; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 104, Folder 10)
    - Construction: F-3 Navy Yard, February 1987 - December 1990; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 104, Folder 11)
    - Construction: F-4, November 1979 - March 1987; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 104, Folder 12)
    - Construction: F-5 Anacostia, February 1987 - October 1993; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 104, Folder 13)
    - Construction: F-6 Congress Heights, August 1993 - October 2000; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 104, Folder 14)
    - Construction: F-7 Southern Ave, June 1998 - October 2000; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 104, Folder 15)
    - Construction: F-8 Naylor Road, January 1998 - October 2000; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 104, Folder 16)
    - Construction: F-9 Suitland Road, January 1998 - October 2000; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 104, Folder 17)
    - Construction: F-10 Branch Ave, January 1998 - October 2000; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 104, Folder 18)
    - Construction: F-11 Branch Ave S&I Yard, November 1999 - September 2002; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 104, Folder 19)
    - Construction: D-7, March 1973 - February 1977; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 105, Folder 1)
    - Construction: D-10, D-11, July 1975 - August 1976; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 105, Folder 2)
    - Construction: D-12 D&G Junction, July 1975 - November 1982; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 105, Folder 3)
    - Construction: E-1, E-1a, November 1984 - December 2000; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 105, Folder 4)
    - Construction: E-1b, E-1c, November 1984 - December 1990; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 105, Folder 5)
    - Construction: E-2, July 1975 - January 1997; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 105, Folder 6)
    - Construction: E-2a, January 1987 - September 1994; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 105, Folder 7)
    - Construction: E-3 1, July 1995 - March 1997; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 105, Folder 8)
    - Construction: E-3 2, March 1997 - September 1999; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 105, Folder 9)
    - Construction: E-4a, November 1994 - September 1999; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 105, Folder 10)
    - Construction: E-4b, March 1995 - June 1998; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 105, Folder 11)
    - Aerial Slide Index, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 109B, Folder 1)
    - 5 Notebooks: Detailed Guide to Slide Archives, Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 109B, Folder 2)
    - Slides Master Index, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 109A, Folder 4)
    - Station/Location I, 1979-1997; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 115, Folders 1-3)
    - Station/Location II, 1979-1997; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 115, Folders 4-5, Box 116, Folder 1)
    - Staff, 1985-1996; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 116, Folders 2-6)
    - Stations, 1985-1996; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 116, Folder 7)
    - Safety Committee Briefing, 05/12/1988; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 117, Folder 1)
    - Escalator Brake Failures and Improvement Programs, 05/17/1990; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 117, Folder 2)
    - WMATA/CSXT Common Corridor Safety Program, 09/05/1996; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 117, Folder 3)
    - Capital Improvement Program, c. 1990-1989; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 117, Folder 4)
    - Sherman Ramey, 1992-1998; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 117, Folder 5)
    - Staff and Patrons, 1992-1995; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 117, Folder 6)
    - Name/Item I, 1994-1997; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 117, Folders 7-9)
    - Name/Item II, 1994-1997; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 118, Folders 1-5)
    - Snow Equipment, 01/1996; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 119, Folder 1)
    - Dupont Escalators, 02/08/1996; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 119, Folder 2)
    - Parking Initiative, 02/08/1996; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 119, Folder 3)
    - FY 97 Capital Improvement Plan, 02/15/1996; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 119, Folder 4)
    - SE Bus, 12/1996; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 119, Folder 5)
    - Facilities, Technology, Maintenance, 1996; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 119, Folder 6)
    - Budget Presentation FY 98, 01/16/1997; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 119, Folder 7)
    - Fiscal 1998-2003 Capital Improvement Program, 02/06/1997; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 119, Folder 8)
    - Bike on Rail, 07/1997; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 119, Folder 9)
    - Glenmont, 11/1997; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 119, Folder 10)
    - Train Cars, 11/26/1997; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 119, Folder 11)
    - Greenbelt Burn Incident, 08/1998; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 119, Folder 12)
    - Greenbelt Derail, 08/1998; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 119, Folder 13)
    - RTRA Greenbelt Yard Ops, 09/1998; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 119, Folder 14)
    - Metro System Map, 2011; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 119, Folder 15)
    - Equipment, Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 119, Folder 16)
    - Vendors, Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 119, Folder 17)
    - 5000 Series Rail Car Design MCI Operating Agreement Glenmont Parking Garage Elevators, Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 119, Folder 18)
    - Vacation, Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 119, Folder 19)
  - Publications, MS2374 Series 1 Subseries 5
    - Preliminary Report to the National Capital Transportation Agency on Rail Rapid Transit on the Virginia Pentagon Route Lafayette Square to Four Mile Run, 1962 November; MS2374 Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 111, Folder 1)
    - Preliminary Report to the National Capital Transportation Agency on Alternate Plans For Rail Rapid Transit Crossings of the Potomac River, 1962 November; MS2374 Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 111, Folder 2)
    - Final Report to the National Capital Transportation Agency on Rail Rapid Transit on the Alexandria-Springfield Route Lafayette Square to Four Mile Run, 1963 March; MS2374 Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 111, Folder 3)
    - Washington Metropolitan Area Transit Authority Adopted Regional Rapid Rail Transit Plan and Program, 1968 March 1; MS2374 Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 111, Folder 4)
    - Technical Appendix Benefits to the Washington Area from the Adopted Regional Metro System, 1968 October 25; MS2374 Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 111, Folder 5)
    - Final Report: The Observed Performance of Deep Subway Excavation Project 1B0011, 1974 September 12; MS2374 Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 111, Folder 6)
    - Remarks given by Warren Quenstedt, Deputy General Manager, Washington Metropolitan Area Transit Authority, 1976 November 9; MS2374 Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 111, Folder 7)
    - Washington Metropolitan Area Transit Authority Compacy, 1984, 1988; MS2374 Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 111, Folder 8)
    - Washington Metropolitan Area Transit Authority System Calendar, 1997-2000; MS2374 Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 111, Folder 9)
    - Washington Metropolitan Area Transit Authority Annual Reports, 1986-1989; MS2374 Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 111, Folder 10)
    - Washington Metropolitan Area Transit Authority Annual Reports, 1990-1991; MS2374 Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 111, Folder 11)
    - Washington Metropolitan Area Transit Authority Annual Reports, 2007-2009; MS2374 Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 112, Folder 1)
    - Washington Metropolitan Area Transit Authority Fiscal Year Budget, 1993; MS2374 Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 112, Folder 2)
    - Washington Metropolitan Area Transit Authority Fiscal Year Budget, 1999; MS2374 Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 112, Folder 3)
    - Washington Metropolitan Area Transit Authority Joint Development Solicitation, 2005 March, August; MS2374 Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 112, Folder 4)
    - Washington Metropolitan Area Transit Authority M: The Magazine of Metro, 1987, 1989, 1992; MS2374 Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 112, Folder 5)
    - Washington Metropolitan Area Transit Authority Transit Expansion Plan, 1999 April; MS2374 Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 112, Folder 6)
    - Metrobus: The First Fifteen Years, 1988; MS2374 Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 112, Folder 7)
    - Metrobus 25th Anniversary, 1973-1998, MS2374 Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 112, Folder 8)
    - Materials related to Metrorail's Twenty-fifth Anniversary, 2001; MS2374 Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 112, Folder 9)
    - Materials related to Metro Stations, undated; MS2374 Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 112, Folder 10)
    - Washington Metropolitan Area Transit Authority Metro Opens Doors, 2007; MS2374 Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 112, Folder 11)
    - In Memory of Jeanice McMillan, 2009 September 29; MS2374 Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 112, Folder 12)
    - Washington Metropolitan Area Transit Authority Customer Guide to Metro Access, 2014 August; MS2374 Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 112, Folder 13)
    - The Economics of Metro, undated; MS2374 Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 112, Folder 14)
    - Metro Ride Guide, undated; MS2374 Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 112, Folder 15)
    - Grand Solicitation produced by Washington Metropolitan Area Transit Authority, undated; MS2374 Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 112, Folder 16)
    - Miscellaneous documents related to Washington Metropolitan Area Transit Authority, undated; MS2374 Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 112, Folder 17)
    - Miscellaneous visual materials related to Washington Metropolitan Area Transit Authority, undated; MS2374 Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 112, Folder 18)
    - Materials related to the construction and operation of Metrorail, 1975-1979; MS2374 Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 113, Folder 1)
    - Publications about Washington Metropolitan Area Transit Authority, 1973, 1976, 1981, 1984; MS2374 Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 113, Folder 2)
    - Passenger Transport: The Weekly Newspaper of the Transit Industry, 1975 March 28; MS2374 Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 113, Folder 3)
    - Publications about Washington Metropolitan Area Transit Authority, 1981, 1988, 1990-1992, 1995; MS2374 Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 113, Folder 4)
    - Publications about Washington Metropolitan Area Transit Authority, 2001, 2004, 2006, 2013; MS2374 Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 113, Folder 5)
    - Headlights: The Magazine of Electric Railways, 1981, 1984-1985; MS2374 Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 113, Folder 6)
    - Washington Building Congress Bulletins, 1991-1992; MS2374 Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 113, Folder 7)
    - Building the Metro: The Project of the Past Quarter-Century, 2000; MS2374 Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 113, Folder 8)
    - A new dimension in transit technology...Washington Metro, Automated by General Railway Signal, undated; MS2374 Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 113, Folder 9)
    - International Publications featuring Washington Metropolitan Area Transit Authority, 1980-1981; MS2374 Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 113, Folder 10)
    - From Here to There by Metrobus: The Official Atlas of Route Maps As of September 10, 1973, 1973 September 10; MS2374 Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 114, Folder 1)
    - Metro Arts: Washington Metropolitan Area Transit Authority Art in Transit Program, 2003; MS2374 Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 114, Folder 2)
    - AIA Journal, December 1975, 1975 December; MS2374 Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 114, Folder 3)
    - International Publications featuring Washington Metropolitan Area Transit Authority, 1976, 1988; MS2374 Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 114, Folder 4)
- Audio/Visual material, Series 2
  - WMATA- VHS, 1996-2002; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - WMATA- VHS, 1996-2002; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - WMATA- VHS, 1996-2002; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Test VHS, 1980-2000; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - A-2 Earth Tunnels (1st Ans. Print), Series 2 (Box 64A, Folder 1)
  - A-2 Earth Tunnels #13, 1982; Series 2 (Box 64A, Folder 2)
  - Bonds, War, Show/ Capital Transit Co./ Chavoe and Mail, Series 2 (Box 64A, Folder 3)
  - Coming Way to Go, Series 2 (Box 64A, Folder 4)